## THEOPHILUS AYANO

A highly skilled and versatile professional with a solid background in full-stack web development and extensive experience as a sales manager. Possessing a unique blend of technical expertise and business acumen, I excel in bridging the gap between technology and commercial success. With a proven track record in both software development and sales management, I bring a valuable perspective to any organization, driving innovation and achieving tangible results.



## **Experience**

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER AND SALES MANAGER PHOENIX INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY 2021-PRESENT

- Develop and maintain professional and in-house web applications
- Collaborate with cross-functional teams to design and implement new features.
- Work closely with project stakeholders to gather requirements and provide technical insights.
- Utilize sales experience to contribute valuable perspectives on user experience, customer engagement, and market demand, resulting in enhanced application functionality and user satisfaction.

#### IT CONSULTANT AND SALES MANAGER BITMAS BAKERY Ltd 2019-2021

- Advised on technology solutions to improve business processes and procedures.
- Utilize sales experience to contribute valuable perspectives on user experience, customer

# FULL STACK DEVELOPER AND IT CONSULTANT ZXT TECHNOLOGY 2017-2019

- Lead end-to-end software developments, from requirements gathering and system design to coding, testing, and deployment, ensuring on-time and withinbudget project delivery
- Advised clients on emerging technologies, industry trends, and best practices, guiding them in making informed decisions regarding their IT infrastructure and digital transformation strategies.



#### PROFESSIONAL CERTIFICATIONS

- ✓ CERTIFICATE IN MANAGEMENT, NIGERIA INSTITUTE OF MANAGEMENT(NIM)
- ✓ CERTIFICATE IN SOFTWARE ENGINEERING, ALX AFRICA
- ✓ CCNA1 CERTIFICATE, CISCO

- Email: kenkszii@gmail.com
- Cell phone: 08066286427
- LinkedIn Profile: linkedin.com/in/kenkszii/
- Portfolio: https://www.sheyi.tech
  - 🥎 Address: Kaduna, Nigeria



### **Relevant Skills**

- HTML
- CSS
- Python
- JavaScript
- ReactJs
- Flask
- Technical documentation
- Lookup portfolio for more: https://www.sheyi.tech



## **Education History**

2021-2023 MBA (finance and investment)

Ahmadu Bello University

2013-2017 BSC (ed). Physics

Ahmadu Bello University

2010-2013 NCE Physics and Computer Sc.

Federal College of Education

Zaria.



## **Specialization**

- ✓ Developer
- ✓ Graphics design
- ✓ Coach
- ✓ Entrepreneur
- ✓ IT Professional
- ✓ Business Manager
- ✓ Business Development
- Customer Relationship Management
- ✓ Digital Marketer



### Referees

Dr Abdulmalik Lawal 07068842881 abdulmaliklawal556@gmail

Zainab Mahmud 09095530681 Zeemahmud16@gmail.com

Prof. Oluwaseyi Abiodun 09074699027 talksheyi900@gmail.com